<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Office</title>
    <link>http://TheOffice.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The Office</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 18:26:38 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://TheOffice.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dunderpedia Basic Stats</title>
      <link>http://TheOffice.org/blog/post1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 18:26:38 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://TheOffice.org/blog/post1/</guid>
      <description>This blog post focuses on providing the full analysis performed during the first part of the project.
We start our Dunderpedia analysis by generating The Office network, which includes all the characters in the Office extracted from the Dunderpedia. The nodes in the network will be all the characters, and we will place an edge between nodes A and B if the Dunderpedia wiki page of node A links to the Dunderpedia Wiki page of node B.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basic Stats: IMDb</title>
      <link>http://TheOffice.org/blog/post9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 23:16:38 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://TheOffice.org/blog/post9/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basic Stats: The Office Transcript</title>
      <link>http://TheOffice.org/blog/post10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 23:16:38 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://TheOffice.org/blog/post10/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Communities</title>
      <link>http://TheOffice.org/blog/post8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 13:26:38 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://TheOffice.org/blog/post8/</guid>
      <description>We would like to see if based on the Dunderpedia network that we have created from the character pages, their relationships/groups can be inferred. For this we will use the Louvain algorithm. Then, based on our knowledge as viewers of The Office, we are going to analyse if these communities make sense.
    Plotly.d3.json(&#34;/communities/0-communities.json&#34;, function(err, fig) { Plotly.plot(&#39;\/communities\/0-communities.json&#39;, fig.data, fig.layout, {responsive: true}); });  We can see that the identified communities make sense based on the characters and their relations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordClouds</title>
      <link>http://TheOffice.org/blog/post7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 13:16:38 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://TheOffice.org/blog/post7/</guid>
      <description>Wordclouds based on Dunderpedia These wordclourds represent the most used words by the 16 main characters based on their Dunderpedia Wiki description.
Due to the accuracy of the word-clouds we can see a small description about everyone just by analyzing the words. Let&amp;rsquo;s look at some of them individually:
  From Angela&amp;rsquo;s wordcloud we can see that she mostly used cat and party, as she loved cats and had a lot of them, and she also was the head of party planning committee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: IMDb </title>
      <link>http://TheOffice.org/blog/post5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 15:26:38 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://TheOffice.org/blog/post5/</guid>
      <description>To better understand the data we are analysising, we will do some basic statistics with the IMDB dataframe.
First, we take a glance at the episode distribution.
    Plotly.d3.json(&#34;/kaggle_imdb/01-episodes_per_season.json&#34;, function(err, fig) { Plotly.plot(&#39;\/kaggle_imdb\/01-episodes_per_season.json&#39;, fig.data, fig.layout, {responsive: true}); }); 
The first season was the shortest with only 6 expisodes. After it, the seasons tend to have between 22 and 26 episodes, except the 4th season with only 14 episodes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: The Office (US) - Complete Dialogue/Transcript</title>
      <link>http://TheOffice.org/blog/post6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 00:26:38 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://TheOffice.org/blog/post6/</guid>
      <description>Character summary of lines spoken and episodes acted We start our analysis on the transcript dataset by looking at the line distribution between characters through seasons and the number of episodes where each character acted. We again look at the 25 main characters identified fom the Dunderpedia Wiki.
Let&amp;rsquo;s now see how many lines the main characters have and in how this varies from season to season:
    Plotly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office Iconic Phrases</title>
      <link>http://TheOffice.org/blog/post11/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 13:26:38 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://TheOffice.org/blog/post11/</guid>
      <description>How many times the characters say their favorite lines? Having watched the office, we cannot help but to analyse the most popular sentences that identify the main characters.
That&amp;rsquo;s what shes said Let&amp;rsquo;s start by looking at Michaels most popular joke: That&amp;rsquo;s what she said.
Since this joke became so popular, we will start by looking at which characters said it throughout all the 9 seasons.
    Plotly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office Character Interactions</title>
      <link>http://TheOffice.org/blog/post12/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 13:26:38 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://TheOffice.org/blog/post12/</guid>
      <description>Character interactions Now that we got to know the characters a little better, we will analayse their relationships based on their interactions in their transcripts. For this, we are going to create a network based on the main character interactions. We define an interaction between two character when one character mentions the other. To analyse the mentions between characters we use the transcript dataset from Kaggle. To limit the complexity of the network, we will only use the main characters based on the Dunderpedia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kaggle dataset: The Office (US) - Sentiment Analysis</title>
      <link>http://TheOffice.org/blog/post4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 21:26:38 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://TheOffice.org/blog/post4/</guid>
      <description>Sentiment Analysis Througout the show each character is exposed to a multitude of feelings, some are in pain and some of them are full of excitement. However, from season to season their perception of awareness is changing and one can not be sure which character is the most positive and who does not share the same enjoyment. To see the variation on the character sentiments, we take a closer look at the transcripts for each character, we can observe which character is the happiest and who has the lowest sentiment score during each season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About the TV series</title>
      <link>http://TheOffice.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://TheOffice.org/about/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Goal</title>
      <link>http://TheOffice.org/goal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://TheOffice.org/goal/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
